{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Fire Damage Restoration Companies","appliedActionRules":{"SDB_SCROLLY_SITE_24719":"SDB_SCROLLY_SITE_24719_ctrl"},"categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"__cache./api/resource/task/interview/40222/":{"taskOID":40222,"originalTaskOID":40222,"setID":529,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":8152,"questionDisplayText":"Is this an emergency?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Is this an emergency?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":1564,"questionDisplayText":"Type of Smoke Damage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"How bad is the smoke or fire damage? (Select all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":2239,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Entire house or structure has burned down","answerDisplayText":"Entire house or structure has burned down","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":582,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"A portion of the building has burned","answerDisplayText":"A portion of the building has burned","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":583,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"A room was damaged","answerDisplayText":"A room was damaged","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4303,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Nothing burned but smoke has coated everything","answerDisplayText":"Nothing burned but smoke has coated everything","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6317,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"There's also water damage from putting the fire out","answerDisplayText":"There's also water damage from putting the fire out","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":1214,"questionDisplayText":"When the Incident Occurred","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"When did the fire occur?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":3091,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Hours ago","answerDisplayText":"Hours ago","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1832,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Days ago","answerDisplayText":"Days ago","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3912,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Months ago","answerDisplayText":"Months ago","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":1449,"questionDisplayText":"Structure(s) affected","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What part of the structure is affected?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5389,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Roof","answerDisplayText":"Roof","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1288,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Ceiling","answerDisplayText":"Ceiling","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6774,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Walls","answerDisplayText":"Walls","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2549,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Floors","answerDisplayText":"Floors","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":1444,"questionDisplayText":"Number of Rooms Affected","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"How many rooms in your home are currently being affected by the damage?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":272,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"1 room","answerDisplayText":"1 room","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":364,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"2 - 4 rooms","answerDisplayText":"2 - 4 rooms","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":499,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"5 - 10 rooms","answerDisplayText":"5 - 10 rooms","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2236,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Entire home","answerDisplayText":"Entire home","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":50001,"questionDisplayText":"Covered by Insurance","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this request covered by an insurance claim?","shortQuestionText":"Covered by an insurance claim?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":7,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":8152,"questionDisplayText":"Is this an emergency?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Is this an emergency?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":1564,"questionDisplayText":"Type of Smoke Damage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"How bad is the smoke or fire damage? (Select all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":2239,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Entire house or structure has burned down","answerDisplayText":"Entire house or structure has burned down","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":582,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"A portion of the building has burned","answerDisplayText":"A portion of the building has burned","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":583,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"A room was damaged","answerDisplayText":"A room was damaged","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4303,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Nothing burned but smoke has coated everything","answerDisplayText":"Nothing burned but smoke has coated everything","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6317,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"There's also water damage from putting the fire out","answerDisplayText":"There's also water damage from putting the fire out","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":2239,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Entire house or structure has burned down","answerDisplayText":"Entire house or structure has burned down","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":582,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"A portion of the building has burned","answerDisplayText":"A portion of the building has burned","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":583,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"A room was damaged","answerDisplayText":"A room was damaged","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4303,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Nothing burned but smoke has coated everything","answerDisplayText":"Nothing burned but smoke has coated everything","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6317,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"There's also water damage from putting the fire out","answerDisplayText":"There's also water damage from putting the fire out","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":1214,"questionDisplayText":"When the Incident Occurred","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"When did the fire occur?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":3091,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Hours ago","answerDisplayText":"Hours ago","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1832,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Days ago","answerDisplayText":"Days ago","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3912,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Months ago","answerDisplayText":"Months ago","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":3091,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Hours ago","answerDisplayText":"Hours ago","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1832,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Days ago","answerDisplayText":"Days ago","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3912,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Months ago","answerDisplayText":"Months ago","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":1449,"questionDisplayText":"Structure(s) affected","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What part of the structure is affected?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5389,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Roof","answerDisplayText":"Roof","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1288,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Ceiling","answerDisplayText":"Ceiling","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6774,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Walls","answerDisplayText":"Walls","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2549,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Floors","answerDisplayText":"Floors","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5389,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Roof","answerDisplayText":"Roof","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1288,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Ceiling","answerDisplayText":"Ceiling","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6774,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Walls","answerDisplayText":"Walls","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2549,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Floors","answerDisplayText":"Floors","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":1444,"questionDisplayText":"Number of Rooms Affected","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"How many rooms in your home are currently being affected by the damage?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":272,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"1 room","answerDisplayText":"1 room","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":364,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"2 - 4 rooms","answerDisplayText":"2 - 4 rooms","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":499,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"5 - 10 rooms","answerDisplayText":"5 - 10 rooms","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2236,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Entire home","answerDisplayText":"Entire home","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":272,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"1 room","answerDisplayText":"1 room","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":364,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"2 - 4 rooms","answerDisplayText":"2 - 4 rooms","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":499,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"5 - 10 rooms","answerDisplayText":"5 - 10 rooms","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2236,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Entire home","answerDisplayText":"Entire home","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":50001,"questionDisplayText":"Covered by Insurance","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this request covered by an insurance claim?","shortQuestionText":"Covered by an insurance claim?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":7,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"__cache./api/resource/task/40222/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":40222,"taskName":"Recovery Service - Fire or Smoke Damage","taskDescription":"Repair Damage or Clean Up After a Fire","xmTaskDescriptor":"Fire Damage Restoration Companies","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":306,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"Recovery Damage Fire Smoke clean","textMessagingName":"Smoke Recovery","rolloverLongDesc":"Includes removal of destroyed items, water \u0026 soot clean-up \u0026 necessary repairs \u0026 painting. These companies are typically familiar with insurance procedures \u0026 practices.","rolloverShortDesc":"Repair smoke, fire \u0026 water damage to roofs, walls, ceilings, floors, etc.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Repair Damage or Clean Up After a Fire.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"Fire Damage Restoration \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Fire \u0026 Smoke Damage Recovery","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":63,"acceptGoal":4,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":0,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Fire or Smoke Damage Recovery","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Recovery Service - Fire or Smoke Damage","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Fire \u0026 Smoke Recovery Project","urlName":"Recovery-Service-Fire-or-Smoke-Damage","taskConsiderationId":2,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":true,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Fire Damage Restoration Companies - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Smoke Recovery","searchKeywords":"Recovery,Damage,Fire,Smoke,clean,after,restoration,cleanup,up","emcCategoryOid":-12022,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":529,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true}